<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DATA-DRIVEN PERSONAL BLOG on RAFAL MAJCHERCZYK</title>
    <link>https://Rafal-Majcherczyk.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DATA-DRIVEN PERSONAL BLOG on RAFAL MAJCHERCZYK</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Rafal-Majcherczyk.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FIFA World Cup 2022 Fan Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://Rafal-Majcherczyk.github.io/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Rafal-Majcherczyk.github.io/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>In the second half of November 2022, I started looking for an interesting data project idea. I did some research and brainstorming and compiled a list of potential topics that I could dive into when, all of a sudden, the FIFA World Cup 2022 started. Watching first matches and observing football fans from all over the world reveling in the World Cup fever I slowly started getting hooked as well. In order to celebrate this event I decided to put in practice my SQL, Python, and Tableau skills and design a dashboard in Tableau Public which would tell a story of our favourite teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIFA World Cup 2022 Predictive Model (article under construction)</title>
      <link>https://Rafal-Majcherczyk.github.io/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Rafal-Majcherczyk.github.io/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Article is currently under construction. However, the model which is the main topic of this post is already available on my Github account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABOUT</title>
      <link>https://Rafal-Majcherczyk.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Rafal-Majcherczyk.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Rafal Majcherczyk. My passion for numbers and quantification led me to study mathematics at AGH University of Science and Technology, where I earned a Master of Science in Applied Mathematics with a major in Financial and Insurance Mathematics. After graduation, I spent several years working in the financial sector in various analytical and managerial positions. During this time, I had an opportunity to work on numerous projects, including initiatives with high-level executive visibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONTACT</title>
      <link>https://Rafal-Majcherczyk.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Rafal-Majcherczyk.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>CONTACT Please use contact details below if you would like to get in touch with me.
Email address: majcherczyk.r@gmail.com (alternatively, you can use an email button that you can find in the top/bottom right corner of the screen to open your email client)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
